UNITE Legislative Department Records 6000/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Background: ITG - Labor Codes, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Background: Women and Unions, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Labor Law Single Plant Rulemaking, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Labor Law - Unions are Good, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Labor Law Republican Attacks - 104th Congress, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Labor - HHS Budget Compliance Amendment, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Labor Law Task Force Notes, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Labor Law - Corporate Campaign Hearings, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Labor Law - NLRB Oversight Hrgs. 104th Congress, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Labor Law - Beck Issue, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Dunlop Commission, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Labor Evolution of Work Committee Labor Law reform, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Labor Law Reform Hoekstra, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Labor Law Reform, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Labor Law - Reform - Alternative Disputes, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Labor Law Reform Articles - 104th Congress, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Labor Law Reform, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Improving Language, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- 8(a)(2) FLAP, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Task Force on 8A-2, 1993-1995 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Local Empowerment & Flexibility Acts H.R. 2086 & S. 88, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Max's Paper on 8(a)(2), 1996 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Labor Law - "Salting", 1995 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Section 8 (a)(2), 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Striker Replacement-Exec. Order, 1995-1996 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Labor Law - Team Act - Senate, 1992-1996 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- 8 (a)(2), 1995-1996 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Women and Labor Law Reform, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Chair Photos, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  4 Photographs
- Medical Bills, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Frequent Flyers, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- ILG Correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- ILGWU News Releases, 1989-1992 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Correspondence, 1988-1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- 1986 ILGWU Convention (Box 35, Folder 7)
- ILGWU History of, 1978-1988 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- '83 ILGWU Convention, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Labels, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Labor History/ Women, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Medical Records, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- ILGWU, History of, 1978-1989 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  1 Cassette Tape moved to box 54 and put into media case
- ILGWU - Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- UNITE! Correspondence, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Organizing, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Previous Employees, 1986-1998 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Personnel, 1990-1995 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Reprints, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- ILGWU 75th Health Center Anniversary, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Fasanella, 1991-1996 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Magazines, 1996-1997 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Bruce Duhran Union Dues, 1990-1996 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Evy's Retirement Party 2/26/97, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Hotel Evy Party, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Evy Roast Scholarship Luncheon 10/7/97, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Dubrow - Personal Dues & Correspondence, 1988-1999 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Dubrow - Contributions - Dues, 1988-1998 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Dubrow - Articles, Tributes, 1976-1999 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Evy's Party 5/4/89, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Papers, 1992-1996 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Dubrow - Boards and Representation, 1994-1998 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- ILGWU Convention, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Evy Dubrow, 1992-1999 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Correspondence Re: Health Records & Credit, 1984-1990 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- African Trade, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Apparel Industry Partnership, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Evy's Bio, 1987-1997 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Canadian Import Problem, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Consumer Federation of America, 1997-1999 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Discuss w/ Jay, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Dubrow Misc., 1986-1997 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Dubrow - Thank You, 1980-1999 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Family and Medical Leave, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Independent Action Company 2000 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- NAFTA Fast Track, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Calendar Events, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Minimum Wage (Dubrow) (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Minimum Wage Leg. 1998-1999 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- National Foundation for Women's Legislators, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Publications - Dubrow, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Senate Info. - Dubrow, 1996-1998 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Senior Summer, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Social Security, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Steve Koplan, 1997-1998 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Sweat Shop Material, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Sweatshop (Dubrow), 1995 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Sweatshops (Dubrow), 1996 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Sweatshops (Dubrow), 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- ILGWU Heritage Fund - 2001 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- United Seniors Health Cooperative, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- USHC, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Women's Party Corp. Lawsuit, 1994-1997 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Booklets, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Misc., 2001 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Americans for Democratic Action, 1998-2000 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Misc., 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Misc., 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Evelyn Dubrow - Misc., 1970-1998 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Salvadoran Sweatshops, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- National Immigration Forum Dinner (Honoring Jay Mazur, April 11), 2000 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Organizations/Support, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- GAP - El Salvador 2002 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Trade: China Textile Agreement, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- China WTO Deal 1999: Textiles & Apparel, 1999-2000 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Papers, 2000-2001 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Ergonomics, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- OSHA: Chemical Safety Board, 1997-1999 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- OSHA Unite Grants, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Safety and Health Issues (107th), 2002 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- "The Washington Post" Article May, 17. 2004 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Point Blank 2003 LOBY Coplain/DHB Industries (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Point Blank 2003 LOBY Coplain/DHB Industries Inc. (Box 39, Folder 12)
- US Chemical Safety Board, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- OSHA: Ergonomics UNITE Materials, 2000-2001 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- UNITE Testimony 106th Congress, 1997-2000 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- UNITE vs. OSHA, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Ergonomics Hearings, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Ergonomics Sen. Breaux Bill 2002 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Ergonomics: UNITE vs. UPS, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Kleen - Brite Labs - NY' 2001 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Made in NY 2001-2001 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Warnaco 2003 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Linens of the Weeks 2002 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Levi Strauss & Co. Plant Closing, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Sweatshops Levi Strauss Policies, 1996-1998 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- K-Mart Lay Offs 2001 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Up-to-Date Violations Laundry, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- GAP, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- UNITE! Sign-On Letters, 1999-2002 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Cornell - WIS Program, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Child Labor New Season, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Point Blank: Correspondence from Army & Dod, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Pont Blank: Workers Affidavits, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Point Blank: Legal Cases & Complaints, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Point Blank: Congressional Letters, 2002-2004 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Point Blank; Press Coverage, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- DSCC, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Democratic Leadership Council, 1990-1996 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Emily's List, 1996-1998 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Garment Industry Development Corp., 2002-2004 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Virginia Latino Coalition, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Washington Office on Latin America, 1999-2005 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Organizations: Congressional Hispanic Caucus, 2004 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- CHC Board Meeting Jan 2004 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Congressional Hispanic Caucus Convention 2004 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Taxes 2001 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Overtime Pay, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Save Overtime, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Medicare Reform Legislation, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Judical Nominations, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- 527 Issue - Steve Rosenthal Constituence Groups, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- UI 108th Congress, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Election Reform, 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Appointment & Participants, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Appointment Requests, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Minimum Wage, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Comp Time & UI, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Immigration, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Lobbying for Trade Unionist, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Legislative Process, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Bankruptcy Bill (2002) (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Bankruptcy, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Bankruptcy Reform Act of 2001 HR333 107th Congress (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Corporate Code of Conduct Act, HR4596, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Corporate Responsibility ENRON, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Corporate Responsibility Field Campaign, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Election Reform 2001: States (Box 42, Folder 14)
- HR 7623 (401k) Law 7/30/02, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Gore Procurement Initiatives, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Miller ENRON - Pension Bill, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Election Reform (HR 3295) (Law 10129), 2002 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Election 2002 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Election 2000 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Election Reform 2002 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Election Reform State Implementation 2003 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- ENRON 2002 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- ENRON, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Stimulus Package Bush Tax Cut 2001 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Stock Options, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- TC2, 1997-2002 (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Remittances from Latin American Workers, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 28)
- Right to Work 2002, 2001-2002 (Box 42, Folder 29)
- Economic Stimulus 2002 (Box 42, Folder 30)
- Welfare Tanf Reauthorization 2002 (Box 42, Folder 31)
- Tanf, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 32)
- WIA Reauthorization 2002 (Box 42, Folder 33)
- Unemployment Insurance Displaced Workers, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 34)
- Unemployment Insurance Reform 2001 - 2002 (Box 42, Folder 35)
- Prison Labor: 105th Congress, 1995-1997 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Prison Labor: FPI Protective Clothing Expansion, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Prison Labor: Recidivision Info, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- FPI Reform, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Prison Labor FPI Board Hearing 2003 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Prison Labor: UNITE Policy, 1994-1997 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Prison Labor: FPI Expansion Proposal 3/97, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Prison Labor: Gary David Martin, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Prison Labor - 107th Congress, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Prison Labor: 106th Congress, 1999-2006 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- IUC, 2002-2003 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Prison Labor: State Initiatives, 1998-2000 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Prison Labor 2001, 2000-2002 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Federal Prison Industries Reports and Miscellaneous, 1990-1993 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Federal Prison Industries Hearings Testimony, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Federal Prison Industries Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- FPI Testimony, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- FPI Board Hearing 1/03, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- FPI - Treasury Aprops 2004 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- FPI Reform HR - 1577 2001-2002 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Prison Labor: Gloves, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Prison Labor HR 926, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Prison Labor: HR 926 House Judiciary Letters, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Prison Labor: HSE. Subcmte. On Crime 8/5/99 Hearing, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Prison Labor: Hse. Subcmte. On Oversight & Investigations, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Prison Labor: Hoekstra Bill 106th Congress (HR 2551), 1999 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Prison Labor: Hoekstra Hearing 4/21/99, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Prison Industry: Hot, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Prison Labor: Industry Coalition, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Federal Prison Industries Hearing 4/18/2002 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- PIE, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Prison Labor: Hoekstra Bill 105th Congress, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Prison Labor: Hoekstra Frank Compromise 2000 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Federal Prison Indust., 103rd Congress, 1993-1995 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Legislation 102nd, 1990-1991 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Prison Labor: Oregon Materials, 1996-1997 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- UNITE Benefitism, 1998-1999 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Prison Labor: Rule Change, 1997-1999 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Prison Labor: Testimony, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Prison Labor: 2000 Work Clothes Expansion (Box 44, Folder 20)
- The Most Key FPI/BDU info., 2000 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Documents, 1998-1999 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Prison Labor: New Bad Issues, 1998-1999 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Work Clothing, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- FPI: Standards and Procedures, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- Ann Hoffman; Prison Labor Testimony May 24, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Prison Labor: UNICOR Definitions & Guidelines, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Prison Labor: McCollum Bill H.R. 2558 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Prison Labor: FPI Statute, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Prison Labor: FPI/DOD Procurement Regs. Questions + Notes, 1998-2000 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Prison Labor: UNICOR Reports (Sales & Annual), 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Prison Labor: Work Clothing Expansion, 1995-1999 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Prison Labor: Legislative History, 1990-1993 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Prison Labor: 106th Congress Levin Amendment, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Prison Labor: Levin Bill 105th Congress S.339, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Prison Labor: Limited, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Prison Labor: Machinists (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Prison Labor: Meese Group, 1995-1997 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Prison Labor: Meeting Notes (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Prison Labor: FPI/DOD Procurement, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Prison Labor: Sleeping Bags, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Prison Labor: T-Shirts, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Prisoners in OSHA, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Prison Labor: Prisoners & FLSA, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Prison Labor: Public Employee Dept., 1997 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Prison Labor: PIE Program Proposed Revisions 1998 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Prison Labor: PIE Program, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Prison Labor: Use in '98 election, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Prison Labor: McCollum Bill, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- House Subcommittee on Crime: June 25, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Prison Labor: National Prison Industries Forum: 5/5/98, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Prison Labor: China, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Prison Labor: Crime Subcommittee Hearing 10/30/97, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Prison Labor: Apprenticeships, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 29)
- Prison Labor: Barney Frank, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 30)
- Prison Labor: Competition in Contracting Act Coalition, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 31)
- Prison Labor: ABA Program 10/99, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 32)
- Prison Labor: AFL-CIO, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 33)
- Prison Labor: Steering Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 45, Folder 34)
- Prison Labor: Prison Blues, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 35)
- Prison Labor: Proposed Rule Change 1999 (Box 45, Folder 36)
- Trade: Vietnam, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Wool Tariffs: Grant Proposal, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Wool Tariffs, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Impact of S. 2338/H.R. 4358 on U.S. Wool Production, 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Wool Tariffs 2000 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Trade: Adjustment Assistance, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Wool tariff: Implementation, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- El Salvadore, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Trade: Fast Track & FTAA 2001: Member Reports (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance 2001-2002 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Fast Track 2001 CTC Briefing (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Fast Track Steel Legacy Clause, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Wool Tariffs: 106th Congress, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Trade Workshop, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- ATPA - Colombia, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- IUC 2003 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Buy American 2003 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Vietnam, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Trade: Transshipment, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Trade: Transshipment, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Wool Tariffs: Press, 1999-2000 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Wool Tariffs: Visits, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Wool Tariff 2001, 2000-2001 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Wool Tariff Implementation, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Textiles - Congressional, 2000-2002 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Trade: Singapore FTA, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Trade: Rules of Origin, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Trade: Senate Finance Meeting with DEB Lamb (Box 47, Folder 11)
- FTAA - Latin America 2002 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Fast Track - 2002 Baucus Alternative (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Wool Tariffs, Testimony/Comments, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Wool Tariffs: Connecticut Problems, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Wool Tariffs: Burlington, 1998-1999 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Wool Tariffs: Amicale Problem, 1995-1998 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Wool Tariffs: Don Johnson Mtg. 3/29/99, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Wool Tariffs 1999 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- TAA: Community Workforce Partnership S-1193 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Wool tariffs: Administration Position, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Wool Tariffs: Background, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Fast Track HR3009 Latino Outreach, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- HR 3005 Fast Track Vote 2002 (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Trade: International Right to Know, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Textile Study 2002 (Box 47, Folder 26)
- trade Pakistan 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 27)
- Trade: Burma, 2000-2001 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Bush Admin. Agenda Labor Rights 2002 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Trade: Berry Amendment - Berets, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Berry Amendment: 2001 Army Beret Flap (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Cambodia Textile Agreement 2002 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Trade: Cambodia, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Andean Trade Preference Act 2001 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Trade - Jordan FTA, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Trade - Jordan FTA, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Andean Trade Promotion Act 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Workers Rights 2002 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Trade 2003 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- China: Textile Safeguards 2003 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- HR 3005 Fast Track Vote 2002, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Turkey Free Trade AGG 2002 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- berry Amendment: DOD Reports, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Berry Amendment 2000 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Berry Amendment 106th Congress, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Wool Tariffs: UNITE Internal Reports 1999 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Wool Tariffs: Draft Bill 2000 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- Wool Fabric Import Quota Men's Tailored Suits, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Trade: Immigration Issues, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- HR 3005 Fast Track Vote 2002 (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Immigration: Fix 96 Criminal Detainees, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Immigration: Fix 96, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Immigration_Section 245(i), 1997-1998 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Immigration: Central America Community, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Immigration: Employment Verification, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Immigration: AIDS, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Immigration: Farmworkers, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Immigration: Agricultural Workers, 1999-2000 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Immigration Driver's License V.S. 2002-2003 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Immigration Issues for 2001 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- H1B's: 106th Congress, 1998-2000 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Immigration: H-1B Plus, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Immigration Security Act of 2002 Joe Baca (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Immigration Hearing: Enhanced border Security & Visa Entry Reform Act Friday, April 12, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Legalization 2002 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Reward Work Campaign 2002 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Social Security No Match 2002 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Studies and Polls, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Immigration Border Security Act HR-1885 2002 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Immigration Hoffman Plastics, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Immigration 2003 H.R. 500 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Sweatshops: Stop Sweatshops Act 2000 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Judicial Nominations, 2002-2003 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Judicial Nominations, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Judicial Nominations Robert Brame for NLRB 2001-2003 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Judicial Nominations Eugene Scalia 2002 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Labor Committee for Trade Negotiations & Trade Policy (LAC), 2002 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- 2002 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Labor HHS Appropriations 2001 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Military Uniforms, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Military Procurement (2002) (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Fix 96 Advocacy Day, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- A Petition to Save Overtime Pay, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  Floppy Disc - Contains the names of the ones who signed the petition.
- Bankruptcy 108th, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 34)
- Burma, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 35)
- Asbestos Legislations, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 36)
- Comp. Time HR-1119 Vote, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 37)
- Employee Free Choice Act Voice @ Work 2003 (Box 49, Folder 38)
- Ergonomics, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Ergonomics 2002 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Sweatshop: Stop Sweatshops Act 107th Congress, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Sweatshop: Stop Sweatshop Act 106th Congress, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Fact Sheets, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Anti-Sweatshop Legislation 2003 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Clinton's White House Initiative 2001 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- GAP - LCLAA Convention 2002 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- GAP Campaign 2002 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Mayflower Laundry 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Background Report: DHB Industries & Securities Violations, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- The DHB Minority Report, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Point Blank Fact Sheet, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Sterling Laundry 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Community Hearing Perez/Fenty, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Community Letter Sterling Laundry, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Service Contract Act Sterling Laundry Strike, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Montgomery County Sterling Laundry, 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Point Blank Quality Summary, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Point Blank: Potential Procurement Law Violations, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Background Report: DHB Industries, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Cintas/Unitog Merger, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- GAP Day of Action Dec 17, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Gucci Event, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- Brylane 2002-2003 (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Global Justice for Gurmen Workers Campaign 2002 (Box 50, Folder 26)
- Hugo Boss Distribution Center Midway, GA, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 27)
- Reward Work Coalition, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 28)
- Walmont Campaign - 2003 (Box 50, Folder 29)
- ILGWU Heritage Fund, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement (LCLAA), 2001 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Low Wage Immigrant Worker Coalition, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- DCCC, 1988-1995 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- CTC/Trade Summits, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- UNITY Partnership, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Faith & Politics Institute, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- GIDC-2003 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Democratic Policy Commission, 1986-1998 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Cornell University, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Consumer Federation of America, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Child Labor Coalition, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Congressional Economic Leadership Institute (CELI), 1999 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Citizens Trade Campaign (CTC) Retreat 2002 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Citizen's Trade Campaign (CTC) (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Congressional Hispanic Caucus Institute, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Congressional Hispanic Caucus Institutes 1999 Issues Conference (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Labor Summit 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- BCLI, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Bert Corona Leadership Institute, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- ATTAC 2002 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Americans for Democratic Action, 1982-2002 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- IUC 2003 (Industrial Unions Council) (Box 51, Folder 23)
- 21st Century Democrats: up to 2003 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Point Blank: Strike 2003 (Box 51, Folder 25)
- Point Blank: Letters to Congress, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Organizations: CBC Institute Conference 2004 (Box 51, Folder 27)